[
  {
    "question": "What behavior change technique is a specific plan that drives behavior by identifying cues toward action?",
    "answer": "Implementation intention",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "a69354f0-d86b-4515-ac15-49cfabdff635"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a behavior change technique where clients list potential barriers and make plans to overcome them?",
    "answer": "Coping responses",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "fedc230a-6728-4031-ab97-e529e3d5910e"
  },
  {
    "question": "Self-esteem and body image are said to have which type of relationship?",
    "answer": "Reciprocal",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "6162b6b6-14c1-4bd5-9044-9672ce9113c4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which leadership component refers to the leader being a great example for how to live a healthy and balanced life, which includes being optimistic, empathetic, and knowledgeable?",
    "answer": "Leader's qualities",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "a061fa07-32f0-4bbd-a3a7-100e700dd3d2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the practice of identifying a negative inner narrative and replacing it with positive statements?",
    "answer": "Reverse listing",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "a6607bc5-36cc-44e2-9912-304a3f010161"
  },
  {
    "question": "Intentions are a good predictor of behavior, but what has been shown to help translate intentions into behavior?",
    "answer": "Planning",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "7403b9e6-5b25-4ff7-add8-15e146bef2fb"
  },
  {
    "question": "A client has been journaling their behavior. They find that if they get home and sit on the couch to watch television, they do not end up exercising. But if they bring their gym clothes to work with them and change before leaving the office, they are more likely to exercise. Which behavior change technique are they using?",
    "answer": "Self-monitoring",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "18f1d5e9-d3d6-454c-97a2-44070c7e3d28"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of imagery occurs when a client imagines health-related outcomes?",
    "answer": "Appearance imagery",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "961417de-7597-441f-aa70-73ce5ffcc52e"
  },
  {
    "question": "If a Certified Personal Trainer helps a client improve their technique by using guided practice to enhance confidence, what determinant of behavior are they targeting?",
    "answer": "Self-efficacy",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "c28417de-c5db-43fc-81d5-2cf2fdd5a476"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a client-centric coaching style that helps enhance their desire to change by resolving ambivalence?",
    "answer": "Motivational interviewing",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "205ef35b-050a-41ca-9c92-b01da4d27777"
  },
  {
    "question": "A Certified Personal Trainer wants to improve a client's outcome expectations for resistance training. What behavior change technique might they use?",
    "answer": "Providing information on the health benefits",
    "tags": [
      "cpt",
      "section 2 quiz"
    ],
    "id": "fdec3de5-9604-4af7-9777-262694b5f6b9"
  }
]